Eugene Michasiw Web Developer

(416) 886-9984 eugene@michasiw.com Toronto, ON

Portfolio: michasiw.com Github: github.com/eugenefm

I am a Web Developer with six years of digital marketing experience in the non-profit sector. I bring a creative background to designing and building responsive, modern web applications.

Skills

HTML5

∃ CSS3

Sass

JavaScript

iQuery

React

T APIs

git Git

GitHub

Node.js

♦ VS Code

G Firebase

Wordpress

Drupal

■ UI/UX Design

Adobe CC

Email Marketing

Online Fundraising

Liquid

MongoDB

Projects

Stockup.ninja

Last Minute Cocktails

Who Wants to be a Dev

An equity research tool that displays financial data and recent news about a company. HTML5, CSS3, React, JavaScript, REST APIs, UI/UX Design

A cocktail recipe app that allows users to log in, search, and save recipes.

Firebase, React, HTML5, CSS3, REST APIs, JavaScript, UI/UX Design

A trivia game that pulls computer science questions from a trivia API.

HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript, REST APIs, UI/UX Design

Experience

Capitalize for Kids

Director of Marketing Jan 2018 - Apr 2019

Jan 2018 - Apr 2019

Marketing Manager

May 2016 - Dec 2017

- Project managed the redesign of the organization's website. Did the initial UI/UX design and managed external developers to complete Wordpress theme customizations. Was responsible for all content and ongoing updates.
- Implemented an online fundraising platform and integrated it with the organization's Wordpress website. Created custom CSS stylesheets for transaction forms, leaderboards, and thermometers.
- Managed all marketing and communications for one of Canada's most important capital markets conferences – an event that raised \$1.5 million for charity in 2018.

Jack.org

Marketing and Communications Lead May 2013 - Apr 2016

- Implemented a new digital fundraising platform for the organization and coded custom CSS stylesheets to match the organization's brand standards.
- Managed email marketing campaigns and designed the organization's email templates.
- Directed a complete rebranding of the organization in partnership with a pro-bono agency and designed a variety of marketing materials to support the new brand.

Education

Queen's University

Bachelor of Arts, Honours, Film and Media Sep 2009 - Apr 2013

HackerYou